<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Beloved</title>
    <link>https://my-beloved.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Beloved</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://my-beloved.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://my-beloved.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my-beloved.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Motivation &amp;ldquo;I thought, this has got to be the least read of all the books I&amp;rsquo;d written because it is about something that the characters don&amp;rsquo;t want to remember, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to remember, black people don&amp;rsquo;t want to remember, white people don&amp;rsquo;t want to remember. I mean, it&amp;rsquo;s national amnesia.&amp;rdquo; -Toni Morrison
This National Amnesia is at the heart of the American story and how we interpret the events of slavery and the events after is how we represent America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circle of Iron</title>
      <link>https://my-beloved.github.io/post/circle-of-iron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my-beloved.github.io/post/circle-of-iron/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I kissed her neck. I didn&amp;rsquo;t choke it. The circle of iron choked it.&amp;rdquo; -Beloved
When confronting the past sometimes we put ourselves in a vulnerable position. The risk is to lose everything, but still we must persist.
By Arnold</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sermon of Embrase</title>
      <link>https://my-beloved.github.io/post/sermon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my-beloved.github.io/post/sermon/</guid>
      <description>Semon of Embrace In the clearing’s hush, Baby Sugg’s voice soars, Her sermon weaves through trees, a sacred plea, A healing force, “Love your hands,” she implores, Echoes of pain, yet hope&amp;rsquo;s symphony free.
“We flesh; flesh that weeps,” Baby Suggs declares, A call to listeners humanity, In the clearing’s space, Beloved despairs, Each word a mantra, filled with clarity.
She warns, “Yonder they do not love your flesh”, Her words a testimony of scars past, While they remember many scars that are fresh, They knew of her truth and her wisdom vast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sethe</title>
      <link>https://my-beloved.github.io/post/painting-of-sethe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my-beloved.github.io/post/painting-of-sethe/</guid>
      <description>I wondered what would happen if the girl from Vermeer&amp;rsquo;s famous painting: “Girl with a Pearl Earring,” was Sethe. Although Vermeer&amp;rsquo;s original painting was a portrait, (painting like photography) changing the subject to Sethe made the painting symbolic. A slave would never have the opportunity to get an earring, let alone a portrait of herself. This paradox was fascinating, inspiring me to draw this painting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketch on Beloved</title>
      <link>https://my-beloved.github.io/sketch-on-beloved/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my-beloved.github.io/sketch-on-beloved/</guid>
      <description>Sketch on Beloved by Ishan Ghosh
Program Notes: Sketch on Beloved was written by Ishan Ghosh in 2023 as a creative response to Toni Morrison’s award-winning book Beloved. He felt entitling it a sketch was appropriate, as it rapidly shifts between various styles, moods, and qualities. Drawing from the styles of David Maslanka, Percy Grainger, Pyotr Tchaikovsky, Igor Stravinsky, Samuel Coleridge-Taylor, this work responds to the thoughts Ishan felt while reading the novel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketch on Beloved</title>
      <link>https://my-beloved.github.io/post/sketch-on-beloved/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my-beloved.github.io/post/sketch-on-beloved/</guid>
      <description>Sketch on Beloved by Ishan Ghosh
Program Notes: Sketch on Beloved was written by Ishan Ghosh in 2023 as a creative response to Toni Morrison’s award-winning book Beloved. He felt entitling it a sketch was appropriate, as it rapidly shifts between various styles, moods, and qualities. Drawing from the styles of David Maslanka, Percy Grainger, Pyotr Tchaikovsky, Igor Stravinsky, Samuel Coleridge-Taylor, this work responds to the thoughts Ishan felt while reading the novel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rose Fertilizer</title>
      <link>https://my-beloved.github.io/post/families/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my-beloved.github.io/post/families/</guid>
      <description>The rose was rotting, the tin was closed. Family is the most important of all, and it will get us through the abyss.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
